hey guys Pastor Meers here uh just
wanted to invite you to check out this
very powerful message on the Kingdom of
Heaven I pray that it'll bless you as
you learn to keep your eyes and your
mind stayed on Heavenly
things
[Music]
last week uh I preached a sermon
entitled The Valley Of The
Shadow today the message is entitled The
Glory of the mountain this is a part two
to last week's
message and over the past uh several
weeks we have been focusing upon this
theme of beholding the Lamb of
God I want to take you to our first
slide because we are going to continue
our focus on this theme of beholding the
Lamb of God and I want you to notice
with me in the book Book of John 1 and
verse
29 the Bible says
Behold the Lamb of God which taketh away
the sin of the
world we have been focused on this idea
this this understanding that what God
desires us to do as Christians as
Believers is really very simple he wants
us to behold
the Lamb of God which takes away the sin
of the world and and as we've been
looking through this theme we we we
decided last week that we were going to
spend 40 days
beholding the Lamb of God now what is
interesting is that as I look at the
comments uh that we have uh everyone
that's been participating and we we've
had many people participating in this
exercise some people jumping in later uh
and and starting you know even
today but as I look at the comments
there is one thing that that that seems
to to to thread through every comment
and it is this how broken how broken we
are by beholding what Jesus did for us
on the cross uh put a one in the chat if
if that has been your experience as you
look at the cross you feel this
Brokenness uh uh you you you feel this
this
unworthiness
because you have taken the
time to be still and Behold the Lamb of
God and this should not be surprising
we're told in the book of Zechariah
12:10 Zechariah 12: 10 the Bible says
here and I will pour upon the House of
David and upon the inhabitants of
Jerusalem the spirit of Grace and
supplication and they shall look upon me
whom they have pierced and they shall
mourn for him as one mourneth for his
only son and shall be in bitterness for
him as one that is in bitterness for his
firstborn it it it seems as if and we
talked about this last week it seems as
if God is saying I need you to be
mentally broken I need you to be
emotionally broken as you as You observe
as you sit still and Behold the Lamb of
God I need you to get to the place where
you become
broken where you
mourn and we learned last week that God
wanted us to mourn for a very simple
reason we saw that according to Matthew
5 and ver4 the Bible says here blessed
are they that mourn for they shall be
comforted God wants to comfort us God
wants to send the Holy Spirit which is
the comforter to comfort us and so
that's what we talked about last week
and that is the experience that that
many of you have been praying
for your praying to mourn you're praying
to feel the anguish you're praying to
understand your own unworthiness and let
me tell you beloved it is not a good
feeling please understand me when you
see how wretched and miserable and blind
and naked you actually are it is it is
not a good feeling to
embrace today's sermon uh uh I'm going
to try to keep it short I know I know
you're thinking Pastor you're not going
to keep this short but I'm going to try
because because as I've mentioned to you
earlier uh in the Sabbath school there
is something that we're going to be
listening to this afternoon uh 5:00
we're going to put the link in alra live
it's a listening party and what you're
going to hear by the grace of God is
going to be so powerful that I'm trying
to hold back in my
sermon I I just want to give you a
little bit I I don't want to take up too
much mental energy for you today because
you're going to need it for this evening
nonetheless we're going to we're going
to go through a very powerful message
today but hopefully
hopefully you will be able to save brain
power for this evening follow
me this verse blessed are they that
mourn for they shall be comforted reveal
something in the context in which was
given let's go to the Book of Matthew 5
and verse 2 where Jesus says these words
he opened his mouth and taught them
saying blessed are the poor in spirit
for theirs is the kingdom of God blessed
are they that mourn for they shall be
comforted blessed are the meek for they
shall inherit the earth blessed are they
which do hunger and thirst after
righteousness for they shall be filled
blessed are the merci f for
they shall obtain Mercy blessed are the
pure in heart for they shall see God
blessed are the peacemakers for they
shall be called the children of God
blessed are they which are persecuted
for righteousness sake for theirs is the
kingdom of heaven now I want you to
notice something and let's just leave
that screen uh uh up for a moment and I
want you to notice something very
powerful here there is a a and B A A
Part A and A Part B in every verse that
we've just read blessed are the poor and
spirit those that mourn those that are
Meek those that hunger and thirst after
righteousness those that are merciful
those that are pure in heart those that
are peacemakers and the end result right
of being poor in spirit and mourning and
meing uh mourning and being meek and and
hungering for righteousness the end
result is the kingdom of heaven
is being comforted is inheriting the
Earth is being filled with righteousness
is obtaining Mercy is seeing God is is
being children of God is inheriting the
kingdom of of heaven so let's come back
you can let's get off that
slide and let me break this down for you
a little bit
more in this A and
B combination of these verses what the
Bible's telling us is those that are
poor in spirit now those that that mourn
now will ultimately be comforted in the
kingdom of
God every B section of the verses we've
just read are results that are obtained
in the kingdom of God so those who are
poor in spirit now those who are poor in
spirit now will inherit the kingdom of
heaven then those who mourn now shall be
comforted then those who are Meek now
shall inherit the earth then those who
are hungry and hungering and thirsting
after righteousness now shall be filled
with righteousness then those who are
merciful now will obtain Mercy when
Jesus comes then those who are pure in
heart now will see God when he comes
then those who are peacemakers now will
be called the children of their Heavenly
Father literally then those who are
persecuted for righteousness sake now
shall inherit the kingdom of heaven then
are you catching this so then the
question is how do we become poor in
spirit and mourn and meek and and hunger
and thirst after righteousness and
become merciful and pure in heart and
peacemakers the way that we become these
things is by
beholding the Lamb of God God which
takes away the sin of the
world please put a one in the chat if
you understand what I just what I just
broke down it is by
beholding the glory of Jesus Christ on
the cross that we
become poor in
spirit that we mourn that we become Meek
that we become hungry and thirsty for
righteousness why because we don't have
it in us that we become merciful that we
become pure in heart that we become
peacemakers if you're with me so far
just give me a a by faith amen so I can
know so so notice this in Galatians
chapter
6:14 we're told God forbid that I should
Glory save in the cross of our Lord
Jesus Christ by whom the world is
crucified unto me and I unto the world
we are
told that the Cross of Christ is the
glory that we should behold the Cross of
Christ is the glory that we should
behold again Romans 1:16 for I am not
ashamed of the gospel of Christ for it
is the power of God unto salvation to
everyone that believeth to the Jew
first and also to the Greek for therein
is the righteousness of God revealed
from Faith to Faith as it is written the
just shall live by faith
so we have come to understand that the
glory of Jesus is the cross and by
beholding the cross that is what
produces mourning within us that is what
produces a poor Spirit within us that is
what produces these
attributes of which the end result is
the kingdom of
heaven we learned
last week about this 40 days where Jesus
was in the wilderness how that was a
type of of Moses lifting up the serpent
in the wilderness John 3:14 the Bible
says and as Moses lifted up the serpent
in the wilderness even so must the son
of man be lifted
up just as the children of Israel
journeyed in the wilderness for 40 years
Jesus journeyed in the wilderness for 40
days he was the serpent on the pole and
in that story we understand that God was
trying to get
us to
experience this this this concept of
Christ coming to Die For Us by beholding
the serpent on the pole in the
wilderness something is supposed to
break our hearts break our
spirits to the point of
mourning and so we''ve been for focusing
on beholding the cross now let me ask
you a question how many of you like to
mourn how many of you like to walk
around sad how many of you like to be
brokenhearted and and and just like what
in the how many of you enjoy that
feeling go ahead and put a five in the
chat if you
enjoy
morning I don't think I'm going to see
any fives in the
chat yeah it's not
fun if you were to go into the
Wilderness for 40 days it would not be
fun many of you are going through this
40-day exercise right now and and I know
for many of you you're you're like Matt
this is not fun I I'm looking at how I'm
beginning to see just how wretched I am
I'm beginning to see just how unlike
Christ I am I can't even
pray I can't even meditate on him for a
few minutes without like me you know
okay I'm I'm tired
now why why is is is is God wanting us
to focus on the lamb so much to the
point where we mourn and as as I said
before it's because he wants to comfort
us but I need y'all to see
something because you see as you all
have been beholding here we go y'all
here we go as we have behold as you have
been beholding the Lamb on the cross and
you see the picture of Christ on the
cross and you see the suffering of
Christ on the cross there is something
about that picture on the cross that
that that we we miss that that that
we're we're not too focused on but we
should be focused on and that is the
fact let's let's go to Matthew chapter
27:29 notice what the Bible says here
and when they had ploted a crown of
thorns they put it on his head and a re
in his right hand and they bowed the
knee before him and mocked him saying
hail King of the
Jews hail King of the
Jews Jesus is wearing a
crown let me say that
again in this picture the image of the
serpent on the pole which is a type of
Christ as we look at the picture of
Christ as he's on the cross he is
wearing a
crown let me say it again he is wearing
a
crown he is wearing a
crown why is that so
significant because beloved when you
think of a crown what do you think of as
a Christian when you think of a crown
what are you hoping for you are
hoping for eternal life
you are
thinking the
Kingdom of
Heaven they call him King on the
cross and so what I'm suggesting to you
beloved is that while God says yes I
want you to behold my son and I want you
to see the the the wounds and I want you
to see the beating and I want you to see
the suffering there is also something
else in that picture and what I want you
to see in that picture is the crown of
Victory laid up for those that Behold
the
Lamb the Bible says in James chapter 1
ver 12 blessed is a man that endureth
Temptation for when he is tried he shall
receive the Crown of Life The Crown of
Life which he which the Lord has
promised to them that love him so
beloved what I want you to understand is
that while we are beholding the Lamb on
the cross listen listen our first
response is we're not looking at the
crown we're looking at the suffering but
God says yes that's what I want you to
do I want you to Behold The Suffering
first so that when I reveal the crown to
you you will be blown
away but you must first go through the
you must first go through the suffering
before you can truly appreciate the
crown are y'all following me so far see
see let me let me allow the spirit to
blow your mind right now remember Jesus
when he comes and begins his mission he
begins it with a 40-day period That's
the 40 days in the wilderness he begins
his ministry with this 40-day period of
suffering suffering and mourning and he
says guys I want you to follow my
example I've come here and I've fought
this battle in the wilderness on your
behalf but I need you to see that as a
Christian you need you need to pick up
your cross and follow
me and that's why we're doing this 40
days of of of meditating upon Christ on
the cross right now are you'all with me
so we're going through this 40-day
period where we're focusing upon the
that 40-day period of suffering but
there is another
40 day period in the Life of
Christ come on y'all let let's go see
what this 40 days is go with me to the
book of Acts chapter 1
verse3 where it says to whom also he
showed himself alive after his Passion
by many infallible proofs being seen of
them how
long how long
y'all 40 days now watch
this 40 days and speaking of the things
pertaining to the kingdom of God now
come back y'all come back oh Lord help
me to remain
calm the first 40
days is
suffering Pastor let's do we're going to
do 40 days of meditating upon Christ
suffering on our behalf him in the
wilderness you know are fasting and and
and all the battle and the struggle and
ultimately pointing to his death but
then there is a second 40-day period and
that second day 40-day Peri second
40-day period is after his
resurrection he has gone to heaven the
reward for those that mourn the reward
for those that are poor in spirit the
reward for those that are Meek the
reward he's G on to Heaven he dies is
buried ascends that first day of the
week goes up to heaven and then comes
back and now he's going to spend 40 days
with his disciples now I need you I need
I need to ask you something let me ask
you what do you think the disciples are
asking Jesus about in those 40
days come on
y'all come
what do you think the disciples are
asking Jesus about in those in those 40
days all right okay hold on
Jesus so you went to
heaven like you were actually there in
heaven what was it
like yes Asante what was it
like now beloved I I don't know about
you but when the text says that Jesus
spent 40 days with the disciples with
his with his people speaking of the
things pertaining to the kingdom of God
I know before I read that and I I'd be
like oh you know he's talking about you
know Salvation and you know and I get
that he was but beloved come on
do you not think the disciples and his
people are like wait a minute can you
tell us what the kingdom of heaven was
like what is it like what does it you
were there you were there there like
there there there yes I was there there
there and I have prepared a place for
you can you
imagine the first 40 days suffering but
he closes his Earthly
Ministry with another 40-day period
after ascending to the kingdom of heaven
now why is this so important to
understand y'all come on let's break it
down come with me to the Book of Exodus
Exodus 24:12 the Bible says and the Lord
said unto Moses come up to me in the
mount come up to me in the mount the
Lord said to
Earl the Lord said to Terry the Lord
said to
latan the Lord said to
zand the Lord said to takora the Lord
said to Ivor the Lord said to to to to
to to Thomas the Lord said to Tina the
Lord said come up to me in the
mount and be there and I will give thee
tables of stone I will give
thee tables of stone and a law and
Commandments which I have written that
thou mayest teach them and Moses went up
into the midst of the cloud Moses went
up into the midst of the cloud Moses
went up into the midst of the cloud
Moses went
up into the midst of the cloud and got
him up in the mount and Moses was in the
mountain 40 days and 40 nights let's see
what happens from Moses being up in
Heavenly places being up in the mount
being up in the mount being up in the
cloud what happens when Moses spends
this 40-day period in the high places
with God what happens Exodus 34:29 and
it came to pass when Moses came down
from the Mount Si with the two tables of
stone in Moses hand and when he came
down from the mount that Moses knew not
that his skin of his face shone
while he talked with
him come on come back
y'all come
back when Moses went up into the mount
up to see the glory of God up in the
mount he came back with his face lighted
up he was
lit his face lit up what do you
think how do you think the disciples
feel after hearing about Jesus's
experience in heaven and he comes back
and he tells them this is what heaven is
like and now if you're
faithful if you're pure in heart if
you're
Meek if you hunger and thir if you
mourn that's going to be your reward
watch
this watch this the Bible says in
Revelation 21:10 come with me Revelation
21:10 he carried me away into the spirit
to a great and high mountain and showed
me the great City the holy Jerusalem
descending out of God from Heaven having
the
what what did the city of Heaven
have it had come on y'all
what did it have it had the glory of God
now Pastor are you telling
me that not
only can we get the glory of God As we
walk through the valley of the
shadow where we're beholding Christ
suffering on the cross that that is his
glory but there's another part of this
there's another 40 days that we're going
to do after this 40 days yes yes yes see
this this 40 days is just focusing on
the valley the shadow of the valley it's
focusing on the sufferings of Christ why
because he's trying to break us someone
said yesterday in in in class that it's
like the military when you go into the
military the first thing they want to do
is break you down
mentally Jesus says the first I need you
to do is I need you to to to have that
shadow of the valley experience where
you are truly broken so that when I show
you the glory the glory of the
mountain the glory of the mountain the
glory of the
city by beholding the glory there by
beholding the reward that comes at the
end of all of
this your character is going to be
changed and now we can begin to to
understand why now we can begin to
understand why Colossians 3:1 says
this if you then be risen with Christ
seek
behold
behold seek those things which are above
where Christ sth on the right hand of
God set your affections on things above
not on things on the earth now come on
let let me break this down for you so
when I was younger my father taught me
and my brothers how to
shoot and you know we we often practice
with the rifle and you got the rifle and
then you got the crosshairs you got the
crosshairs you got the
crosshairs the crosshairs are
designed not as the end
but it is the the method whereby you
focus on the
target just put a five in the chat if
you understand what I just broke down so
so when you're looking through when
you're looking through the scope of the
gun if you will you got the crosshairs
and the crosshairs the scope the you're
not focused necessarily you're focused
on the crosshairs but the crosshairs is
is is trying to get you to pinpoint your
focus on whatever the target is and
beloved listen to me Christ came and
died on the cross so that we would look
up and as we look up at the cross here
is and we're suffering we're saying what
have I done we're saying look at what my
sins have done and we begin to mourn and
we begin to weep we begin to say man I'm
unworthy that when we get to that place
where we have so been broken down it is
then that we're like wait a minute and
we begin to look beyond the cross and we
begin to see whoa the cross is trying to
focus our attention on things above if
you then be Ry with Christ seek those
things which are above where Christ sits
on the right hand of God set your
affections on things above not on things
on the earth whoa so wait a minute the
serpent on the ground that were biting
the children of Israel the Reason God
had the serpent put on a pole and lift
it up was so that they would not look on
the Earth but they would look up to the
serpent on the pole and once we train
our eyes to to behold the serpent on the
pole it places us in a it's a dead
center G dead
center we become dead centered on Heaven
you cannot miss heaven when you're
looking through the crosshairs of the
cross
you can't miss it it is impossible
because Christ doesn't miss the
target sin is missing the
target so so so then what what I'm
trying to tell you beloved is that God
is trying to get our attention on
Heavenly things this is why the book of
Hebrews chapter 11:9 says this by faith
he sojourned in the land of that is
Abraham sojourned in a Land Of Promise
as in a strange country dwelling in
Tabernacles with Isaac and Jacob The
Heirs with him of the same promise for
he looked for a city which has
foundations whose Builder and maker is
God beloved we're supposed to be looking
for a city whose Builder and maker is
God the Bible says in Hebrews 11:27 by
faith he that is Moses forsook Egypt not
fearing the Wrath of the king for he
endured as seeing him who is invisible
but
Beloved the Saints of old had their
minds focused on Heavenly things now why
is this significant come come with me to
Revelation
13:8 the Bible says here and all that
dwell upon the Earth shall worship Him
whose names are not written in the Book
of Life of the lamb slain from the
foundation of the world I don't know if
y'all caught that
God wants us to focus on Heavenly things
why because
all that dwell on the earth will end up
worshiping the
Beast so we got two options we can
either
dwell we can either dwell on Earthly
things or we can dwell
in Heavenly
places we can either look up or we can
look
down see the devil's trying to get us to
look down man look at all these serpents
look down Jesus is trying to get us to
look
up this concept is all through the Book
of Revelation notice again with me
Revelation 13:12 he exercised all the
power of the first Beast before him and
call the Earth and them which dwell
therein to worship the first Beast whose
deadly wound was healed where are you
dwelling Revelation 15:14 and deceiveth
them that dwell on the Earth by the
means of those Miracles which he had
power to do in the side of the Beast
saying to them that dwell on the earth
that they should make an image to the
Beast everyone that dwells upon the
Earth is going to make an image to the
Earth Earth is going to find themselves
outside the kingdom of God how about
this Revelation 14:6 this is why the
Bible says in Revelation 14:6 and
I saw another angel fly in the midst of
Heaven having the Everlasting gospel to
preach unto who those that dwell on the
earth stop dwelling on the earth and
look up
dwell in Heavenly
places dwell upon things that are above
not on things on the earth Revelation
17:8 the Beast that thou sawest was and
is not and shall Ascend out of the
bottomless pit and go into predition and
they that dwell on the Earth shall
wonder whose names were not written in
the Book of Life from the foundation of
the world when they see the Beast that
was and is not and yet is beloved I need
you to understand
this is why this is why the Bible says
in Revelation 13:6 that he that is this
Antichrist power opened his mouth and
blasphemy against God to blaspheme his
name and his Tabernacle and them that
dwell in heaven well who is it that's
dwelling in heaven the Bible just told
us that in Christ we are lifted up into
Heavenly places meaning beloved that you
and I ought to be dwelling on the things
of the kingdom of
God we ought to be dwelling in Heavenly
places our minds need to be thinking
about the city of
Heaven listen John 16:13 the Bible says
how be it when he the spirit of Truth is
come he will guide you into all Truth
for he shall not speak of himself but
whatsoever he shall hear that shall he
speak watch this and he will show you
things to
come what are the things to come Luke
11:2 he said unto them when you pray say
our father Father which are in heaven
Hallowed be thy name thy kingdom
come thy kingdom come the holy spirit is
trying to keep get our minds focused on
the
glory of the
mountain come on y'all can you imagine
spending 40
days
after we have finished our 40 days our
walk through the shadow of the valley
then God says I want you now to spend 40
days meditating on the city of God the
kingdom of God now y'all still don't get
what I mean so let me break it down
Isaiah 26:2 the Bible says open ye the
gates that the righteous nation which
keepeth the truth may enter in th will
keep him in perfect peace whose mind is
stayed on thee because he trusteth in
thee so watch this y'all we're told that
if our minds are stayed on Christ where
is Christ now he's seated in Heavenly
places which means God wants our minds
to be stayed in Heavenly Places come on
let's break it down Ephesians chapter
2:1 and you has he quickened who were
dead in trespasses and sins wherein time
pass ye walked according to the course
of this world according to the prince of
the power of the air
the spirit that now worketh in the
children of Disobedience among whom we
all had our conversation in times pass
in the lust of the flesh fulfilling the
desires of the Flesh and of the mind and
were by Nature the children of Wrath
even as others but God who is rich in
Mercy for his great love where with he
loved us watch this even when we were
dead in sins has quickened Us
Together by grace are you saved and has
raised us up together together and made
us
sit together in Heavenly places in
Christ Jesus that in the ages to come he
might show the exceeding Riches of his
grace in his kindness toward us through
Christ Jesus for by grace are you saved
through faith and that not of yourselves
it is the gift of God I need you to
understand that what God is trying to do
is he's trying to show us the kindness
that he has extended toward us watch
this
by showing us Heavenly
places he's like look I need y'all to
see what I have prepared for
you I need y'all to meditate I need
y'all to focus on what I have prepared
for you I need you to come up like Moses
came up and I need you to take a look by
faith around the city I need you to
understand what I have planned for you I
need you to by faith think on the rich
ites that I have prepared for
you and then we can begin to understand
Isaiah chapter 6 watch this in the year
that King Uzziah died I also saw the
Lord sitting upon a throne remember
Isaiah is caught up and sees the Lord on
his throne in Heavenly places and the
Bible says I saw the Lord sitting upon a
throne high and lifted up and his train
filled the temple above it stood the
seraphim each one had six wings with
Twain he covered his face and with Twain
he covered his feet and with Twain he
did fly and one Cried unto another and
said holy holy holy is the Lord of hosts
the whole earth is full of his glory and
the post of the door moved at the voice
of him that cried and the house was
filled with smoke then said I woe is me
for I am undone because I am a man of
unclean
lips and I dwell I dwell I
dwell I dwell in the midst of a people
of unclean lips for mine eyes have seen
the king the Lord of hosts then flew one
of the seraphim unto me having a live
coold in his hand which he had taken
with with the tongues of the Altar and
he laid it on my mouth and said Lo this
has touched thy lips and thine iniquity
is taken away and thy sin purged watch
this y'all do you realize that when we
by faith
look into the Heavenly realm where Jesus
is
like Isaiah we will have an experience
where we say woe is me I am undone and
what
happens he touches our lips and causes
our iniquity to be purged that is
justification by faith you
guys as we behold the glory of the city
of God and we realize how can I even be
worth any of this in it humbles Us in
the
dust wo is me I'm undone you got this
for me and one of my worship thoughts
this past week as I was looking at the
cross and I put this in in the group it
was like looking at the
picture I I I heard the voice of the
Lord say look at what you
did look at what you
did and in that same
picture of Christ on the cross look at
what your sins did to him and in that
same image the Holy Spirit then says and
now look at what he
did look at what you you know when your
parents say look at what you did and you
get that sense
of God says look at what you
did and then that same picture on the
cross he says now look at what he did
look at what his death provided for you
and so in one instance we mourn look at
what I've done look at what look at what
my sins have done but in that next
instance I'm unworthy Lord you did this
for me all of this is for
me you see what I need you to understand
beloved is that Christ in his ultimate
glory is in heaven and the Bible tells
us in ezek in Exodus 33:20 it said it
says this thou can not see my face for
there shall no man see me and
live I don't know did y'all catch that
just
now no man can see me and
live in my unveiled Glory you can't see
me and live so what is God asking us to
do he's asking us to by
faith see him in his unveiled glory in
heaven and what happens is we
die when by faith we Behold The Glory
that is in that City the glory of of God
when we by faith behold the glory of the
city we
die our faces become lighted
up
now let me still help you here because
all of this right now that I've been
doing is
just we just been setting the foundation
we're almost done but I just need y'all
to catch this okay cuz we don't think
about like we may we might think a
little bit about heaven but then we're
like okay yeah time to get back to the
world and we got to focus on work and we
got to focus on you know this and that
and that we got to focus on the things
of the
earth so we don't really take much time
focusing on the city on the kingdom of
heaven but now many of you have been
taking the time to say wait a minute I
never really focus on the I talk about
the cross I sing about the cross but I
never took time to actually focus on
Jesus on the cross just F just be still
and listen and
watch and man in this watching
activity I have learned
more about the cross in the last seven
days than I
have for a very long
time because I actually took the time to
focus come on Revelation
21 Revelation 21
and I saw a new Heaven and a new Earth
for the first Heaven and the first Earth
were passed away and there was no more
sea come on yall let's break this down
do you
understand that when God recreates the
world ah Lord help me when God recreates
the
world there's no more sea now he didn't
say there's no more water he just said
there's no more sea I need you to
understand this give me how many of you
know what percentage of the world is
water come on y'all what percentage of
the world is made up of
water
70% of the world is
water 70% of the world is
unusable come on you
guys God is saying when I recreate the
Earth it's not going to be 70%
water so imagine the land mass that's
going to why is he doing that because
he's making a kingdom unlike anything we
have
seen did you know that of the the the
the 20 30% of the world that is land we
occupy only 50% of
that
so I just need you to
understand when God says there no more
sea it's because there's going to be
such a great
multitude there's going to be such a
great
multitude that are
redeemed come on y'all he's peopling it
up not only that but watch this Malachi
4:2 but unto you that fear my name shall
the son of righteousness arise with
healing in his wings and you shall go
forth and grow up as calves in the star
so what I need you to understand
belov is that in the New
Jerusalem we are not going to be
stagnant we're going to be
growing in wisdom in
understanding I don't know if y'all
catch this I don't know if y'all spent
time thinking about this
but imagine the land mass that is now
going to be present for mankind and then
in that land mass with all the these
these these the place are populated with
the
redeemed we are going to be
learning learning
what what are we going to be studying
how many of you like music
how many of you like music let me put a
one in the chat if you like
music do you know what happens when we
get to heaven when the earth is
recreated and the same creative God that
created us is now going to say to us you
like music all right here's the School
of Music go ahead and go go
get you're going to be learning how many
of you like
biology how many of you like studying
plant
life come on how many of you how many of
you enjoy chemistry or or or enjoy
poetry or enjoy right listen
y'all because we don't take
time to actually meditate on the kingdom
of God on the glory of the city listen
to
this listen to
this from Advent is home page
549 speaking about the Kingdom of Heaven
here's what it says
there every Power will be developed
every capability increased the grandest
Enterprises will be carried for the
grandest
Enterprises
what grandest what grandest Enterprises
have you thought about that we be
carried forward the loftiest aspirations
will be
reached the highest Ambitions
realized and still there will arise New
Heights to surmount new wonders to
admire new truths to comprehend fresh
objects to call forth the power of body
and mind and soul
man what would happen if you actually
spent time thinking about the place that
you want to be your new
home see the problem is most of us spend
most of our time dwelling on the
earth we might think oh you know I can't
wait to get to heaven it's going to be
great and then we leave it there well
I'm not even going to try to think about
it because the Bible says it has not
entered into your mind so you may as
well not even think about it but God
says set your affection on things above
be thinking about what you man you know
what when I get up there here's the
things I want to do here's the things I
want to do because Beloved the more we
think about the things up there is the
less we will think about the things down
here are y'all catching what I'm saying
the Bible says in Revelation chap 1 ver
6 we're almost done Revelation 1:6 the
Bible says here Revelation 1:6 that God
Bible says here and he has made us Kings
and Priests unto God and his father to
be glory and Dominion to him be glory
and Dominion forever and ever Revelation
510 he has made us unto our Gods Kings
and Priests and we shall reign on earth
now hold on a second hold on a
second we shall what on
Earth we shall rain on
Earth so you mean on
Earth there's going to be cities not
just a city but cities
and Nations oh oh oh let me show you
Revelation 21:4 come on y'all Revelation
21:24 and the nations of them that are
saved shall walk in the light of it and
the kings of the earth do bring their
Glory and Honor into it so let me ask
you a
question what is a nation a nation is
going to have within it
cities communities wait a minute Pastor
there going to be cities on not just the
city of God the New Jerusalem but
there's going to be cities Yes
Y'all cities wait a minute so if there
cities Michelle we haven't even gotten
to the travel the other worlds yet but
if there's cities on
Earth you mean we're going to still get
to travel to one city here and one city
there and that city is going to have
like very unique things about their city
and this city is going to have their
unique and this city is going to have
their uni and the unique ways in which
they create which they make their food
and this city over here and that Nation
over there how they may and there's
there's still going to be things as cult
wait a minute culture hold on so you
mean you mean the new Earth is going to
be like a real
place with a real
sky and a real ground and real
cities Lord how come I don't think about
this place that I want to be so why am I
why is my mind stayed
on Earthly
things come on
Sharice come on different
foods now listen y'all if Jamaican food
is as bomb as it is in a sinful
world are y'all catching
me come on can you imagine the diversity
and the culture and and the things that
we're going to experience a and let's
just let's just that's just this by the
way by the way just think about this the
Bible says that all the nations are
going to bring their Glory
Glory into the into the New
Jerusalem it's almost like God is saying
the New Jerusalem is going to be like a
world
fair so so you know when they have a
world fair people from different nations
nationalities come and they bring their
they bring the things that make their
nationalities unique can you imagine
that beloved in the Kingdom of Heaven
you're seeing all these nationalities
and the things that they specialize in
and it's all brought together
under the context of the glory of
God come
on now now watch this y'all 40 Days in
the Valley I'm broken what have I done
what was me God wants that but he says
when you truly experience that when you
get to the 40 days of the glory of the
mountain it's going to be like wait what
and then you're going to look here
you're going to you know what the
suffering is worth it
yes the things that I may need to suffer
now is worth it because if this is so
then
Wow Come on y'all if this is so then
then then then then this is going to be
amazing I'm going to get to study the
creative powers of God I'm going to get
to study biology and Science and the
animal kingdom and and and I'm going to
get to to study time and love ology you
know Jesus what he did on the cross for
us that's a science all in itself I'm
going to get to study
that and listen y'all the same God
Exodus 31 notice with me notice with me
oh oh no no no no we got to read this
from the light to from light to light
God is leading his people he liveth in
light unapproachable but is surrounded
by 10,000 time 10,000 and thousand of
thousand thousand thousands of holy
happy beings every one of them waiting
to do his bidding they are not inactive
but in communication with other worlds
and all God's vast Dominion this little
world is but an atom of the Lord's
Dominion
now I like going to
Hawaii and every time I go to Hawaii
it's like you know I'm there for 10 days
but man I wish I was there for like a
month because the stuff that I'm seeing
as Taj and watti here taking us around
and they're like oh you got to come here
you got to and it's always like man
there's never enough time to like go
check out everything that's in Hawaii
that's
Hawaii an island a group of islands I I
need y'all to understand beloved if this
world is just an
atom like a
speck in God's unseen the what we cannot
see right now can you
imagine all right listen I'm going to
spend you know the first 1 billion years
just studying Earth cuz this new Earth
and the stuff that God has put on it I'm
so I just I just I know y'all go on to
you know that Galaxy and that univer
I'll be I I'm coming I need to stay here
right now when I'm done then we can go
to the next
one I need y'all to
imagine the glory that God had and now
look at this
Earth and you really telling me that the
things of this Earth are worth missing
out on
that
really listen you the Bible says by
beholding we become
changed how much
time do do you actually
spend dwelling in Heavenly
places allowing the spirit of God to
take you on a tour of Heaven because
that's
what do you understand what I what I'm
saying now look I know what y'all are
thinking right now Pastor let's begin
this 40 days right now and I'm saying
listen just let's go through the valley
first let's go through the valley first
let's let's enter into that you know
Jesus that that's what he did at the
beginning of the ministry we're starting
here there's where our 40 days are at
the end of his ministry here's where the
40 days are let's understand what it
means y'all to be broken to to be
humbled in the to to to mourn to
understand the depth of the sacrifice
and how unworthy we are because of
because of our sins let's get that let's
get the woe is me not a fake wo is me
the fake wo is me is going to is not
going to appreciate the glory of God
blessed are they that mourn for they
shall be
comforted all
right so what are we going to do after
our 40 days of praying through the
valley of focusing on Christ on the
cross is done we're going to take the
next 40
days
we're going to take the next 40 days
y'all now if you're in I want you to put
in the chat just like last week I'm
in am
in we're going to take that next 40 days
and all we're going to do is focus on
the glory of the city of God and beloved
I promise you that the more you focus on
the glory of the city of God your
eyes the things of this world are going
to grow
strangely
dim
strangely dim
now I have been telling you that we are
going to have a special
listening party in
about an hour and a half
now and I'm still not going to tell you
what it is but for those of you that
want to get
on and and listen
to what we're going to listen to uh
we're going to put the link up in the
chat we're not doing alter live like
we're actually uh we've actually
cancelled the after glow or pushed it
back because I need you to have time to
you know settle your
mind and do whatever you need to do and
then we're going to come back and we're
going to listen to something that I
promise you beloved is going to by the
grace of
God spiritually lighten your
face with the glory of God
so um we're going to close in
prayer uh there you go we're going to
put that link up in the
chat and
um praise God praise God for what he has
prepared for
us praise God
for the
Majesty of that
Kingdom that he is prepared because he
loved
us so just
know yes God is calling us to
mourn but it is for a greater
purpose may we all be in that Kingdom
together let's pray Heavenly Father
we thank you for showing us not only
Jesus's 40 days in the wilderness but
his 40 days with his disciples after his
Ascension Lord two different aspects of
the same Plan of
Salvation one one dealing with suffering
the other dealing with joy unspeakable
joy and so Lord help
us help us to keep our our
minds on the crosshairs of the
cross that we may ultimately focus our
attention on the Heavenly places you
have prepared for us thank you Lord for
hearing and answering this prayer
because we ask it in Jesus name amen and
amen